One Love Manchester is a music film directed by Hamish Hamilton.
Live coverage of the concert set up by Ariana Grande at Old Trafford cricket ground
to benefit those affected by the May 2017 Manchester bomb attack.
Performers include Ariana Grande, Justin Bieber, Coldplay, Katy Perry, Take That, Pharrell Williams,
Niall Horan, Miley Cyrus, Usher, Robbie Williams, Little Mix and The Black Eyed Peas.
Self, played by Ariana Grande.
Self - Host, played by Sara Cox.
Self - Host, played by Ore Oduba.
Self - Backstage Host, played by Anita Rani.
Self - Backstage Host, played by Nick Grimshaw.
Self, played by Mac Miller.
One Love may refer to:
The film explores themes of concert, concert film, manchester, tribute show.